export default { 
  "id": "grade-10-spanish-11132024-part1",
  "grade": 10,
  "subject": "Language Arts",
  "title": "Spanish Chapter 4",
  "timeLimit": 30,
  "topic": "grade-10-spanish-11132024-part1",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "tree",
      "options": ["el árbol", "el arbusto", "la hierba"],
      "correctAnswer": "el árbol"
    },
    {
      "question": "forest",
      "options": ["el bosque", "el desierto", "el lago"],
      "correctAnswer": "el bosque"
    },
    {
      "question": "sky",
      "options": ["el cielo", "la nube", "el mar"],
      "correctAnswer": "el cielo"
    },
    {
      "question": "crater",
      "options": ["el cráter", "el valle", "la colina"],
      "correctAnswer": "el cráter"
    },
    {
      "question": "desert",
      "options": ["el desierto", "el océano", "la montaña"],
      "correctAnswer": "el desierto"
    },
    {
      "question": "star",
      "options": ["la estrella", "la luna", "el sol"],
      "correctAnswer": "la estrella"
    },
    {
      "question": "grass",
      "options": ["la hierba", "el árbol", "la planta"],
      "correctAnswer": "la hierba"
    },
    {
      "question": "flower",
      "options": ["la flor", "el árbol", "la planta"],
      "correctAnswer": "la flor"
    },
    {
      "question": "lake",
      "options": ["el lago", "el río", "el océano"],
      "correctAnswer": "el lago"
    },
    {
      "question": "moon",
      "options": ["la luna", "el planeta", "la estrella"],
      "correctAnswer": "la luna"
    },
    {
      "question": "nature",
      "options": ["la naturaleza", "la cultura", "la ciencia"],
      "correctAnswer": "la naturaleza"
    },
    {
      "question": "cloud",
      "options": ["la nube", "la lluvia", "la niebla"],
      "correctAnswer": "la nube"
    },
    {
      "question": "stone",
      "options": ["la piedra", "la roca", "el suelo"],
      "correctAnswer": "la piedra"
    },
    {
      "question": "plant",
      "options": ["la planta", "el árbol", "el arbusto"],
      "correctAnswer": "la planta"
    },
    {
      "question": "river",
      "options": ["el río", "el lago", "el mar"],
      "correctAnswer": "el río"
    },
    {
      "question": "jungle",
      "options": ["la selva", "el bosque", "el desierto"],
      "correctAnswer": "la selva"
    },
    {
      "question": "jungle",
      "options": ["la jungla", "el bosque", "el desierto"],
      "correctAnswer": "la jungla"
    },
    {
      "question": "sun",
      "options": ["el sol", "la luna", "la estrella"],
      "correctAnswer": "el sol"
    },
    {
      "question": "trail",
      "options": ["el sendero", "el camino", "la carretera"],
      "correctAnswer": "el sendero"
    },
    {
      "question": "land",
      "options": ["la tierra", "el cielo", "el agua"],
      "correctAnswer": "la tierra"
    },
    {
      "question": "valley",
      "options": ["el valle", "la colina", "la montaña"],
      "correctAnswer": "el valle"
    },
    {
      "question": "volcano",
      "options": ["el volcán", "la colina", "la montaña"],
      "correctAnswer": "el volcán"
    },
    {
      "question": "animal",
      "options": ["el animal", "la planta", "el ave"],
      "correctAnswer": "el animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "bird",
      "options": ["el ave", "la planta", "el animal"],
      "correctAnswer": "el ave"
    },
    {
      "question": "bird",
      "options": ["el pájaro", "el gato", "el pez"],
      "correctAnswer": "el pájaro"
    },
    {
      "question": "cat",
      "options": ["el gato", "el perro", "la vaca"],
      "correctAnswer": "el gato"
    },
    {
      "question": "dog",
      "options": ["el perro", "el gato", "el ave"],
      "correctAnswer": "el perro"
    },
    {
      "question": "fish",
      "options": ["el pez", "el ave", "el gato"],
      "correctAnswer": "el pez"
    },
    {
      "question": "cow",
      "options": ["la vaca", "la cabra", "la oveja"],
      "correctAnswer": "la vaca"
    }
  ]
};
